{
    "name": ".\\Italian\\Gianluigi9.json",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la ciliegia",
            "failed": 13,
            "lastAsked": 1517941019.758982,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cherry\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 16
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il piattino",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517940965.2535226,
            "question": "Given the definition \"saucer\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lavare",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517940958.0243967,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to wash\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "il grappolo",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517941015.4390972,
            "question": "Given the definition \"brunch\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "abbondante",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1517941011.9402845,
            "question": "Given the definition \"abundant, plentiful\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "di solito",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517940961.884365,
            "question": "Given the definition \"usually\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "l'armadietto",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517940998.1487072,
            "question": "Given the definition \"cupboard\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la passione",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1517940955.5418425,
            "question": "Given the definition \"passion\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "pezzettino"
            ],
            "answer": "il pezzettino",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517941128.5688024,
            "question": "Given the definition \"small piece\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "succoso",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1517941141.130898,
            "question": "Given the definition \"juicy\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "la macedonia",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517941061.7910447,
            "question": "Given the definition \"fruit cocktail\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fruit cocktail",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517941108.908815,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la macedonia\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "spiegare",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1517941137.661535,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to explain\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "small piece",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1517941112.2711992,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il pezzettino\"?",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sbucciare",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1517941114.8700264,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to peel\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "favorite",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517941081.5074255,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"preferito\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dividere",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517941179.9498763,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to divide, share\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "before",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1517941175.4084394,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"prima\"?",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "delicious",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941169.7544394,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"delizioso\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "brunch",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941157.0756445,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il grappolo\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rotondo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941183.185103,
            "question": "Given the definition \"round\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to peel",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941172.1310678,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"sbucciare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "prima",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941185.5826256,
            "question": "Given the definition \"before\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dovere",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941177.6198208,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have to, must\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "usually",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941236.0035286,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di solito\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to cut",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941238.2159798,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"tagliare\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "zucchero"
            ],
            "answer": "lo zucchero",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941231.580539,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sugar\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "a che ora?",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941240.8096228,
            "question": "Given the definition \"a what time?\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to have dinner",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941217.9009392,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"cenare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cherry",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941226.2463908,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la ciliegia\"?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cenare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941233.408549,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to have dinner\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ovale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1517941223.4162724,
            "question": "Given the definition \"oval\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "must do",
                "must"
            ],
            "answer": "to have to, must",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941262.3236785,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dovere\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to explain",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941275.6060507,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"spiegare\"?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "small plate"
            ],
            "answer": "saucer",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941258.483798,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"il piattino\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tagliare",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941244.4497857,
            "question": "Given the definition \"to cut\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cupboard",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941270.2311313,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"l'armadietto\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "oval",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941264.184984,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"ovale\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dopo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941249.0613966,
            "question": "Given the definition \"after\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "preferito",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941253.4201014,
            "question": "Given the definition \"favorite\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "abundant"
            ],
            "answer": "abundant, plentiful",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941299.9404774,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"abbondante\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "to wash",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941281.4709496,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lavare\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "passion",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941286.2946053,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"la passione\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "usually",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941283.7760496,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"di solito\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "what time?",
                "at what time"
            ],
            "answer": "a what time?",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941279.4469008,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"a che ora?\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "after",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941290.1761193,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dopo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "round",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941288.3918238,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"rotondo\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dolce",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941297.1304271,
            "question": "Given the definition \"sweet\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "di solito",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941302.5842264,
            "question": "Given the definition \"usually\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sweet",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941318.016638,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dolce\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "to divide"
            ],
            "answer": "to divide, share",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941304.742237,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"dividere\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sugar",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1517941306.87181,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"lo zucchero\"?",
            "tried": 3
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "delizioso",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941331.5605378,
            "question": "Given the definition \"delicious\", what is the word?",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "juicy",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1517941328.6063387,
            "question": "What is the definition of \"succoso\"?",
            "tried": 4
        }
    ]
}